





Summary

Jump to Section

Having 5.5 years of total IT experience including 3.5 years of experience Robotics Process Automation BluePrism, Decipher OCR, Automation Anywhere, IQ Bot and Python and 2 years of Experience in Automation/Manual Software Testing for multiple Healthcare and Finance domain Clients.

Good Exposure to SDLC in RPA Blueprism.

Good Exposure to Design Solution Design Documents.

Good Exposure to Agile Methodology

Good Exposure to Intelligent Automation using Decipher

Good exposure in Interacting and liaising with Technical and non Technical Business stakeholders.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Work Experience

Wipro Limited as Senior Software Engineer -RPA Sep 2018 to Till Date

Senior RPA Developer, experienced in Creating Solution Design Documents, End to End development of Business Processes.

Cognizant Technologies Solutions as RPA Developer Apr 2015 to Aug 2018

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Shamli Institute of Engineering & Technology, Shamli in 2014

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: AD01 Blueprism Automation Anywhere Advance Certificate

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
BluePrism	6.8	2020	3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

C, C#, SQL			
HP ALM			
SELENIUM			
Facets, MS SQL, Squids			
OCR Decipher	1.1	2020	1 Year(s)
Automation Anywhere			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English		✓	✓	✓
Hindi		✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Humana Inc

Client: Humana

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Dec 2017 - Jun 2018 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: #5 Project Description Automating Windows Application Humana GCP(Guidance Care Portal).

Project Consists of the Following Modules.

- Downloading the Excel Files from outlook having patient details to a File path.
- Getting the Patients details from the Excel File from a File path.
- Loading that data to Collections and then to Queue management.
- Automating the Process to Load the data GCP Portal.

Role RPA Developer Environment/Tool BluePrism Database SQL Server 2008

Project Title: Humana Inc

Client: Humana

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Aug 2017 - Dec 2017 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: #4 Project Description: Automating the Healthcare member registration process enrolled in different plans like Medicare, Medical, Medicaid and Dental on My Humana web portal.

Project consists of the following Modules.

- Unzipping the Excel Files to a File Path.
- Getting the Member details from excel files from a file path.
- Loading the data to collections and then add to Queue management.
- Automating the Web portal to enroll those members in different health plans.

Role RPA Developer Environment/Tool BluePrism Database SQL Server 2008

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Analysis and Understanding the Requirements.
- Designed the Workflow in Blueprism Tool.
- Wrote C# Code to Unzip the Folders.
- Unit and System Testing.

Project Title: Humana Inc

Client: Humana

Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Feb 2017 - Jul 2017 Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: #3 Project Description: Automating the process of Loading the MS Word Files data having SSN Details for different Health care Plans to collections, segregating the SSN with blank values and having values and sending them in different excel files using outlook.

Role RPA Developer Environment/Tool Blueprism

Roles and Responsibilities:

- Analysis and Understanding the requirements.
- Designed the WorkFlow in Blueprism Tool.
- Unit and System Testing.
- Project Title: Wellmark Client: Wellmark Technologies Nature of Employment: Full Time

Duration: Apr 2015 - Jan 2017

Project Details: #2 Project Description: Automating the IDV Agent Portal using Selenium Webdriver. IDV is an Agent portal that enrolls members in different Health care Dental and Vision Plans.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.